# **Ehsan Hosseiny Pajouh**

**Unity Developer** 

## Email - Linkedin - itch.io - Youtube

## **SUMMARY**

I'm a Unity Developer with more than seven years of experience in creating games and applications for Windows, Android, VR and AR. I have skills in Unity, C#, C++, Blender and other software. I have a master's degree in computer engineering with a major in artificial intelligence and several awards in robotic and game development competitions. I like video games and I would love to join a game company. I'm enthusiastic to develop video games and work on exciting projects and make a great time for gamers.

Please feel free to check my itch.io page and youtube channel to see some of my projects.

#### EXPERIENCE

September 2023 - Present

## **Enlightened Robot Entertainment** · Contract - Technical animator

• animated the environmental objects related to the stage and the background of the "Naser: son of man".

May 2022 - Aug 2023 (1 year 4 months)

## Barana Studio · Full-time - Unity Developer and animator

- Programmed an application to diagnose simple diseases and prescribe authorized drugs. Link
- Created a video wall animation for an exhibition.
- Built a simple balloon game that was played with Kinect v2. Link
- Made some mini games and interactive applications for exhibitions.

## May 2019 - May 2022 (2 years)

### Freelancer - Game Developer

- Made and published a retro 8-bit style game that was named "ESI: space thieves" for Windows PC. Link
- Developed a mobile VR earthquake simulator with Google VR for Android.
- Made a VR hospital emergency simulator with HTC Vive for PC.
- Developed a VR meeting room with Photon Pun v2.
- Programmed a mobile game for kids education named "Shadab and Shangool" for Android. Link
- Built a runner game with Kinect v2 for Snapp company for the Elecomp 2019 exhibition. <u>Link</u>
- Made a face filter application with Unity and OpenCV for the NovoNordisk Company exhibition. That makes the user's face fat. <u>Link</u>
- Create a paint gallery exhibition demo application for Windows. Link
- Made an AR Cat game for people who have cat phobia. The game looks like an AR Tamagotchi. Link
- Made a persian word game for android that is named "AbPash". Link
- Working on a clone of the Starfox game for Android that is named "CyberStar". Link
- Working on a third person character controller. Link

### May 2018 - April 2019 (11 months)

#### Carnik Group · Full-time - Unity Developer

- Built an exhibition simulator demo. Players can walk into the environment and talk to virtual persons.
- Developed some applications for Irancell in the Telecom 2018 exhibition included games, wall visual effects, product surveys and product selling.
- Made some photobooth and games with Unity and Kinect V2 for Novo Nordisk events.
- Programmed a 3D environment viewer application for Novo Nordisk company for Android. That application had AR and FPS mode too. <u>Link</u>

### August 2016 - September 2017 (1 years 1 month)

## Mew Games · Full-time - Unity Developer

- Programmed a game that was a clone of PianoTiles and named "Avataz". Link
- Worked on "DirinDirin" mobile game series.

## October 2015 - July 2016 (9 months)

## **AnadSanat** · Full-time - C++ Developer

- Worked on a security device that was installed on post trucks and sent some information like location, temperature, door status and camera image.
- Made an application for windows with C++ and MFC that used all security device functions for clients.

## November 2014 - August 2015 (9 months)

## **Artman** · **Part-time** - *C*++ *Developer*

• Made an application with C++ and OpenCV that detects face points and sends them to Unity to animate game characters face by player face.

### SKILLS

**Programming Languages:** C#, C++, JavaScript **Game Engines:** Unity, Game Maker studio **Software Frameworks:** Three.js, Pixi.js

Other Software: Blender, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere, Adobe XD, Adobe Animate, TVPaint Other Skills: Git, OOP and SOLID programming, prototyping, 2D and 3D animation, UI/UX design

Soft Skills: Team Work, Creativity, Flexible, Communication, Problem-solving, Fast learner

## **EDUCATION**

2014 - 2018	MASTER OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING, MAJOR IN ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE
-------------	--

Azad University, Science And Research Branch

2011 - 2013 BACHELOR OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING, MAJOR IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Kavosh University

2007 - 2009 Associate of Computer Engineering, Major in Computer Engineering

Azad University, Islamshahr Branch

## AWARDS

2010 FIRST PLACE OF RAAD	CUP ROBOTIC COMPETITION
--------------------------	-------------------------

- 2010 KHWARIZMI YOUTH AWARDS FIRST PLACE AT ROBOTIC
- 2010 SECOND PLACE OF AUTCUP ROBOTIC COMPETITION
- 2011 WORTHY OF APPRECIATION IN FIRST STUDENT GAME DEVELOPER FESTIVAL
- 2013 4TH PLACE IN SECOND STUDENT GAME DEVELOPER FESTIVAL
- 2021 AWARD IN AMATEUR SECTION IN THE 5TH INTERNATIONAL BIENNIAL BOOK CARTOON CONTEST-IRAN